Introducing Closet, the first ever all-in-one data analytics tool,
communication platform, product development collaboration system,
digital asset management system, virtual asset marketplace,
and portfolio management tool for apparel designers and creators alike.
Thanks to Closet's state-of-the-art features and capabilities,
you're able to communicate, collaborate,
and attain a seamless digital workflow like never before.
Excel your business through effective communication and collaboration
throughout the entire organization and supply chain.
Purchase and upload readily available design components in the open marketplace
to create unique, high-quality garments
and enhance the productivity of your design process
by checking finished products
in 360-degree view
and by creating real-time rendered images for quality control.
Save time and costs
through 100% accurate,
automized tech pack
and line sheet generation,
rendering, processing, and management
all within Closet.
Increase customer satisfaction
by allowing customers to try on your garments virtually
by using their individual measurements before purchasing
or even before the garment is produced.
Significantly lower your online return rate
and predict the demand before the actual garment manufacturing process
by embedding Closet's fitting viewer on your e-commerce site.
Thanks to Closet,
the design process is more transparent and traceable
from start to finish for all parties involved,
truly revolutionizing the way we communicate and collaborate in fashion.
Closet, the world's largest,
the largest clothing brand
and the largest clothing brand in the world.
The first Closet.
Closet.